22tracks.com 2013-07-29

# 22tracks – blog » Privacy Policy

### [Privacy Policy](http://blog.22tracks.com/privacypolicy/ "Permanent Link to Privacy Policy")

We (“22tracks.com”) know that you care about how your personal information is used and shared, and we take your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. By visiting 22tracks.com website located at http://22tracks.com (the “Site”), you are accepting the practices outlined in this Privacy Policy.

**What Does This Privacy Policy Cover?**  
This Privacy Policy covers 22tracks.coms treatment of personal information that is gathered when you are on the Site and when you use 22tracks.com services (the “Services”). This policy also covers our treatment of any personal information that 22tracks.com’s business partners share with 22tracks.com. This policy does not apply to the practices of third parties that 22tracks.com does not own or control, or to individuals that 22tracks.com does not employ or manage.

**What Personal Information About Customers Does 22tracks.com Collect?**  
Our primary goal in collecting personal information is to provide you with a friendly, customized, and efficient experience. We collect the following types of information from our users:

**Information You Provide to Us**  
We receive and store any information you enter on the Site, enter into Twitter, Facebook or provide to us in any other way. You can choose not to provide us with certain information, but then you may not be able to take advantage of many of our Site’s features. The personal information you provide is used for such purposes as responding to your requests for certain services, customizing the content and advertising you see, and communicating with you about specials, surveys and new products and services. In order for you to use our Site, you are not required to register; however, you must register to take advantage of certain features of the Site, such as bookmarking favorites and other information to appear on your dashboard. To register, you must provide your Twitter, Facebook or Google username and password.

**Automatic Information**  
We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. 22tracks.com automatically receives and records certain “traffic data” on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, 22tracks.com cookie information, and the tracks or genres you requested. 22tracks.com uses this traffic data to help diagnose problems with its server, analyze trends and administer the Site.

Generally, our service automatically collects usage information, such as the numbers and frequency of visitors to our Site and its components, similar to TV ratings that indicate how many people watched a particular show. In addition, we may provide statistical information, not information about you personally, to our partners about how our users, collectively, use our Site. We share this type of statistical data so that our partners also understand how often people use their content and our Site, so that they, too, may provide you with an optimal web experience.

**Information From Other Sources**  
For purposes such as improving personalization of our service, we may receive information about you from other sources and add it to our account information. Like the information you provide to us, we do not share this information with anyone except authorized third parties in connection with providing you with our Service.

**What about Cookies?**  
Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and tell us how and when tracks on our Site are listened and by how many people. 22tracks.com cookies do not collect personal information, and we do not combine information collected through cookies with other personal information to tell us who you are or what your username or e-mail address is.

The “help” portion of the toolbar on the majority of browsers will direct you on how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to command the browser to tell you when you receive a new cookie, or how to fully disable cookies. We strongly recommend that you leave the cookies activated, however, because cookies enable you to take advantage of some of the 22tracks.com’s most attractive features.

Some of our business partners may use cookies on our Site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies.

**Will 22tracks.com Share Any of the Information it Receives?**  
Information about our users is an integral part of our business. We plan to neither rent nor sell your personal information to anyone. We share your personal information only as described below.

**Affiliated Business We Do Not Control**  
In certain situations, 22tracks.com may provide services, or promote products jointly with affiliated businesses, including on the Site. We will share customer information that is related to such transactions with that affiliated business. We require our affiliates to provide the same level of privacy protection that we do.

**Protection of 22tracks.com and Others**  
We may release personal information when we believe in good faith that release is necessary to comply with the law; enforce or apply our conditions of use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of 22tracks.com, our employees, our users, or others. 22tracks.com may disclose personal information to parties in compliance with 22tracks.com’s Copyright Policy, as the 22tracks.com in its sole discretion believes necessary or appropriate in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringement, piracy, or other unlawful activity.

**Can Children Use 22tracks.com’s Services?**  
22tracks.com is not intended for children. If you are under 18, you may use the Site only with involvement of a parent or guardian.

**Conditions of Use**  
If you decide to visit the Site, your visit and any possible dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and application of Dutch law.

**Third Party Sites**  
The Site may permit you to link to other websites on the Internet, and other websites may contain links to the Site. These other websites are not under 22tracks.com’s control. The privacy and security practices of websites linked to or from the Site are not covered by this Privacy Policy, and 22tracks.com is not responsible for the privacy or security practices or the content of such websites.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**  
22tracks.com may amend this Privacy Policy. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used.

**Questions or Concerns**  
If you have any questions or concerns please see our [contact](http://blog.22tracks.com/about) information.
